...kind of situation.
(Howard:)So my friend Leonard
is gonna take you home.
(Girl:)Oh, okay. Let's go, friend Leonard.
(Leonard(answering phone):)- Okay.
- I'll call you.
STEPHAN IE:
Yeah. So are you a scientist like Howard?
LEONARD:
No one's a scientist like Howard.
(Howard:)My mother is so gonna love her.
(Sheldon:)How nice. Maybe they can carpool
when they visit you in federal prison.
(Girl:)I'm sorry, I totally interrupted you.
What were you saying?
- Just said Howard's a terrific guy.
- Yeah.
He's got a great sense of humor.
(Leonard:)He loves his mother a lot.
(Leonard:)Some people say too much.
- I really like that you're such a loyal friend.
- Yeah, I am loyal.
(Leonard:)You know, if you look at the big picture.